{"data":[{"question":"By the time winter comes we _____ the crops.","a":"will have collected","b":"will collect","c":"will be collecting","d":"are collecting","answer":"1","explain":"\n+ Expresses the idea that something will occur before another action in the future. It can also show that something will happen before a specific time in the future\n+ Structure: S+ will\/shall +have+PP\n+ Sign word: By the time","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"21","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"I'll be back by 6. They ______ by then.","a":"will have finished","b":"have will finished","c":"will had finished","d":"will had f inish","answer":"1","explain":"\n+ Expresses the idea that something will occur before another action in the future. It can also show that something will happen before a specific time in the future\n+ Structure: S+ will\/shall +have+PP\n+ Sign word: By 6\n","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"21","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"By the time the children come I will _____ the beds.","a":"make","b":"have made","c":"have make","d":"made","answer":"2","explain":"\n+ Expresses the idea that something will occur before another action in the future. It can also show that something will happen before a specific time in the future\n+ Structure: S+ will\/shall +have+PP\n+ Sign word: By  the time\n","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"21","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"By this time tomorrow we _____ the match.","a":"will have seen","b":"will see","c":"will be seen","d":"are seeing","answer":"1","explain":"\n+ Expresses the idea that something will occur before another action in the future. It can also show that something will happen before a specific time in the future.\n+ Structure: S+ will\/shall +have+PP\n+ Sign word: By  the time\n","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"21","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"By this time tomorrow the mateh ______.","a":"will start","b":"have started","c":"be started","d":"will have started","answer":"4","explain":"\n+ Expresses the idea that something will occur before another action in the future. It can also show that something will happen before a specific time in the future.\n+ Structure: S+ will\/shall +have+PP\n+ Sign word: By  the time\n","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"21","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"By the lime they arrive we'll ______ the coffee.","a":"have made","b":"have make","c":"had made","d":"had make","answer":"1","explain":"\n+ Expresses the idea that something will occur before another action in the future. It can also show that something will happen before a specific time in the future.\n+ Structure: S+ will\/shall +have+PP\n+ Sign word: By  the time\n","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"21","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"By the time the Smiths come hack he'll ______ to hed.","a":"have gone","b":"have go","c":"has gone","d":"had gone","answer":"1","explain":"\n+ Expresses the idea that something will occur before another action in the future. It can also show that something will happen before a specific time in the future\n+ Structure: S+ will\/shall +have+PP\n+ Sign word: By  the time\n","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"21","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"She ______ all the letters by now.","a":"will type","b":"will be typing","c":"will have typed","d":"won't typed have","answer":"3","explain":"\n+ Expresses the idea that something will occur before another action in the future. It can also show that something will happen before a specific time in the future\n+ Structure: S+ will\/shall +have+PP\n+ Sign word: By  now\n","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"21","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"By the time you read the paper I'll ______ two cigarettes.","a":"have smoked","b":"had smoked","c":"had smoke","d":"have smoke","answer":"1","explain":"\nFuture perfect:\n+ Expresses the idea that something will occur before another action in the future. It can also show that something will happen before a specific time in the future.\n+ Structure: S+ will\/shall +have+PP\n+ Sign word: By the time\n","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"21","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"Next week they ______ married for 10 years.","a":"will have be","b":"will have been","c":"will be","d":"have been","answer":"2","explain":"\nFuture perfect:\n+ Expresses the idea that something will occur before another action in the future. It can also show that something will happen before a specific time in the future.\n+ Structure: S+ will\/shall +have+PP\n+ Sign word: (By the time) next week\n","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"21","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"}]}